Most AI agent workflows
trust what a model says it is.
Sol Ultra Gearbox
verifies what actually ran.
It routes Codex work to
typed Sol, Terra, and Luna roles.
Then it checks the real model,
reasoning effort, sandbox,
lineage, token usage,
and filesystem scope from
persisted runtime metadata.
If anything is missing or
mismatched, it fails closed.
The built-in doctor validates
six role profiles.
Dry-run previews global changes,
while managed apply includes rollback.
This release passed twenty-three tests
and a six-role runtime smoke test.
If your team needs multi-agent workflows
you can audit, reproduce, and reverse,
try Sol Ultra Gearbox on GitHub.